Welcome back to another video, guys.
大家欢迎回到新的视频。
Today we are learning English in the
今天我们在落基山脉学习英语。
Rocky Mountains.
>> It's brisk out here. Very sticky. A
这里很冷。非常潮湿。
moose.
一只驼鹿。
>> Their coffee gets sold in Alberta.
他们的咖啡在阿尔伯塔省有售。
>> We are at Radium Hot Springs to make
我们现在在拉迪乌姆温泉，准备生火用的引火物。这里是加拿大海拔最高的城镇。
kindling for the fire. It's the highest
town in Canada.
开始计数单词，出发。
>> Start the word count and let's go.
那么，这个地方以什么闻名？
>> So, what is this place famous for?
他们以咖啡闻名。他们是一家加拿大烘焙厂，这里是他们在不列颠哥伦比亚省的分店。
>> They're famous for their coffee. They
他们的咖啡遍布加拿大吗？
are a Canadian roastery and this is
嗯，他们的咖啡在阿尔伯塔省有售，我猜应该遍布各地。既然我们是咖啡爱好者，来这里真是个不错的享受。我要一杯卡布奇诺。
their location in British Columbia.
那么，加拿大美式咖啡是纯黑咖啡吗？
>> Are they all over Canada?
它是美式咖啡。
>> Uh their coffee gets sold in Alberta and
好的。嗯，我也来一杯。
I'm presuming all over all over the
他们的咖啡都是外带的吗？
place. And seeing that we are coffee
lovers. Uh it's a nice treat for us to
come. I'll have a cappuccino, please.
And then is the Canadiano just black
coffee or
>> it's an American.
it's an American.
>> Okay. Yep. Okay. I'll have one of those.
Okay. Yep. Okay. I'll have one of those.
>> And are they just there to go?
And are they just there to go?
>> It's it's to go. We'll have it to go.
是外带吗？我们要外带。
Yeah, we'll just take it to go.
是的，我们就外带。
>> 8 12 or 16.
8、12还是16。
>> Um
嗯
12. I'll take the 12 for that one.
12。我要12盎司的。
>> Perfect.
完美。
>> Okay. Thank you very much.
好的，非常感谢。
Is that your cappuccino?
那是你的卡布奇诺吗？
We have a cafeteria for Maria.
我们为玛丽亚准备了自助餐厅。
>> Yes. Thank you so much. Here you can
是的，非常感谢。你可以
have a look at it.
看看这个。
>> It's really good. Cheers.
真不错。干杯。
>> Okay. How's your coffee?
好的，你的咖啡怎么样？
>> It's delicious. It is kicking horse
很好喝。这是Kicking Horse
coffee, but it actually says kickass.
咖啡，但它实际上写的是Kickass。
>> And how's your one?
你的咖啡怎么样？
>> It's uh Canadian.
是加拿大产的。
>> Canadian.
加拿大的。
>> Okay. So we got kicking horse coffee.
好的，我们喝的是Kicking Horse咖啡。
This is a very popular coffee in Canada
这是加拿大非常受欢迎的咖啡，
and it was founded in 1996 here in
创立于1996年，就在
Invamir BC. And uh it's one of the best
不列颠哥伦比亚省的Invermere。它是
places to work in Canada. And how is
加拿大最佳工作场所之一。你的咖啡怎么样？
your coffee? That's a strong coffee or
这是浓咖啡吗，还是怎样？
what?
>> It's strong. That's why only I can only
这咖啡很浓。所以只有我只能喝一杯普通的。
drink a normal cup. I can't drink a
我不能像有些人那样喝一桶。这个是8盎司的。
bucket like some people do. So this is a
是的。我们在Inir的Kicking Horse这里快速停了一下，买点咖啡。
8 oz in.
我个人不喝咖啡，所以我没买。
>> Yeah. That was just a quick quick uh pit
哦，你展示了吗？
stop here in Inir kicking horse to get
我爸妈展示了。
some coffee. I don't drink coffee
是的，我们也买了一些咖啡，路上喝。
personally, so uh I didn't get any.
那是咖啡豆还是咖啡粉？
>> Oh, and did you show?
这是咖啡粉，因为我没带咖啡磨豆机。
>> My mom and dad did.
哦，
>> Yeah, we bought some coffee, too, for
好的。现在我们回到露营车了。
the road.
那我们走吧。
>> Are those coffee beans or coffee
走吧。
grounds?
外面挺冷的。
>> These are coffee grounds cuz I don't
我们去湖边吧。
have my mill, my coffee mill with me.
走吧。
Oh,
今天风很大。我只看到…
>> okay. But now we're back at the camper
okay. But now we're back at the camper
van. So,
>> let's go.
let's go.
>> Let's go.
Let's go.
It's brisk out here.
Let's go to the lake.
>> Let's go.
Let's go.
>> There is a lot of wind today. I only see
There is a lot of wind today. I only see
one person out on the lake kayaking.
湖上有一个人在划皮划艇。
This reminds me of the homes along the
这让我想起了不列颠哥伦比亚省海岸线上的房屋，
BC coast like especially in all those
尤其是在那些
like uh small islands and stuff. All
小岛屿上。所有那些房子。
those houses.
>> Yes.
是的。
>> And this this beach is very rocky. This
这个海滩非常多石头。
is a very rocky beach. See all those
这是一个非常多石头的海滩。看到那些
pebbles? Like a small rock like this.
鹅卵石了吗？像这样的
This is called a pebble. A small rock
小石头就叫鹅卵石。像这样的
like this is called a pebble. But yeah,
小石头叫鹅卵石。是的，
this water is uh water is pretty choppy.
这水面挺波涛汹涌的。
The water is pretty choppy. If the water
水面挺波涛汹涌的。如果水面
was smoother and calmer, I would be able
更平静、更平滑，我本可以
to skip this. But it's pretty choppy
把这石头打水漂。但现在水面
right now. So, I don't think I could
很波涛汹涌。所以，我觉得我
skip it. No.
不能打水漂。不行。
>> Look, it's all rocks in there, too.
看，那里面全是石头。
>> Yeah. And you can see this you can see
是的。你还能看到这些，你能看到
this foam.
这些泡沫。
All this foam along along the shoreline.
沿着岸边的这些泡沫。
What is the What is this foam? I just
这泡沫是什么？我刚问了Chachi BT，
asked Chachi BT. So, we'll see uh what
所以我们看看
this foam is along the shoreline.
这岸边的泡沫到底是什么。
>> Natural lake. Okay. So, the foam you see
自然湖泊。好的，那么你看到的泡沫是...
along the shoreline is natural lake foam
沿着海岸线的是天然的湖泊泡沫
forms when organic material in the water
形成于水中的有机物质
like decomposed plants, algae, and other
如分解的植物、藻类和其他
natural matter breaks down and releases
天然物质分解并释放出
compounds called surfactants. These
一种叫做表面活性剂的化合物。
surfactants lower the surface tension of
这些表面活性剂降低了水的表面张力。
the water. So, when the waves and wind
所以，当波浪和风
stir the lake, bubbles form and gather
搅动湖水时，气泡形成并聚集
into foam. So, it's harmless. It's
成泡沫。因此，它是无害的。
caused by the wind and the waves making
这是由风和波浪造成的，
it build up and it sticks to where the
使泡沫积聚并附着在水与陆地交界处。
water meets the land. So, it's just
所以，这只是湖水自然形成的。
formed by the lake. It's nothing nothing
没有什么坏处。你可能甚至可以吃，
bad. You could probably eat it, but I
但我不建议这么做。
would not recommend that.
天气挺冷的，我们回去吧。
It's pretty cold. Let's head back.
我不知道所有好天气都去哪儿了。
I don't know what happened to all the
昨天天气很美好。
nice weather.
今天，
>> Yesterday was beautiful.
这里总是这样吗？
Today,
不。我们上次夏天来这里时，
>> is it always like this here?
湖面很平静。我们在这里吃了冰淇淋，
>> No. The last time we were here in the
天气很美。
summer, it was the lake was calm. We had
我们走吧。
ice cream here. It was beautiful.
>> Let's go.
Let's go.
>> English opens doors to jobs,
英语为工作、友谊、旅行等打开大门。但
friendships, travel, and more. But the
最难的部分是每天都能找到人练习口语。
hardest part is finding someone to
这就是 Easy Speak AI 的用武之地。随时随地进行真实的口语练习。
practice with every single day. That's
拥有12位以上的 AI 导师，你可以选择氛围，
where Easy Speak AI helps. Real speaking
友好、专业或随意。
practice anytime, anywhere. With 12 plus
课程实用，侧重于
AI tutors, you choose the vibe.
旅行、健康对话等你实际会用到的生活技能和真实交流。
Friendly, professional, or casual.
哦，我觉得我晕船了。我感觉不舒服。我们给 Ava 打个电话吧。嘿，
Lessons are practical. They focus on
Ava。我真的感觉不舒服。我觉得我晕船了。所以，我想让你帮我练习去
real life skills like travel, health
药店时的对话。
conversations, and real life chats you
你现在具体感觉怎么样？
actually use. Oh, I think I'm seasick. I
现在我只是感觉非常恶心。头痛得厉害，感觉头晕。
do not feel good. Let's call Ava. Hey,
你有没有感觉出汗或者有点虚弱？
Ava. I really don't feel good. I think I
我确实感觉挺虚弱的。
have seasickness. So, I want you to help
你还有其他症状吗，比如…
me practice for when I go to the
pharmacy.
>> What exactly are you feeling right now?
What exactly are you feeling right now?
>> Right now, I'm just feeling very
Right now, I'm just feeling very
nauseous. My head is pounding. I feel
dizzy.
>> Are you also feeling clammy or perhaps a
Are you also feeling clammy or perhaps a
bit weak?
>> I do feel quite weak actually.
I do feel quite weak actually.
>> Do you have any other symptoms like a
Do you have any other symptoms like a
cough or sore throat?
咳嗽或喉咙痛吗？
>> No, I don't have a sore throat and uh I
不，我没有喉咙痛，而且
don't have a cough either.
我也没有咳嗽。
>> That's good news. Are you experiencing
这可是个好消息。你有没有发冷或者感觉特别
any chills or feeling particularly
疲倦？几乎想整天睡觉那种。
tired? Almost like you could just sleep
我没有发冷，但确实感觉很疲倦。
all day. I am not feeling chills, but I
他们可能还会问你这些症状持续了多久，
am feeling very tired.
以及有没有什么能让症状好转或加重。
>> They might also ask about how long
这感觉像是真实的对话。
you've had these symptoms and if
导师反应自然，纠正迅速，
anything makes them better or worse.
每次课程都能建立自信。
>> This feels like a real conversation. The
一切都个性化定制。设定你的目标和兴趣，
tutor responds naturally, corrects you
应用会为你调整所有内容。
fast, and builds confidence every
复习标签准确显示你的进步情况。
session. Everything is personalized. Set
每天只需5分钟。想象一下
your goals and interests, and the app
三个月后你的英语会达到什么水平。
adapts everything for you. The review
更自信，交流更流畅，
tab shows exactly how you're improving.
关键时刻不再犹豫。
5 minutes a day is all it takes. Imagine
如果你准备好自信开口，
where your English can be in 3 months.
请通过我描述中的链接或置顶消息下载Easy Speak AI。
More confidence, smoother conversations,
and no hesitation when it really
matters. If you're ready to speak with
confidence, download Easy Speak AI using
the link in my description or pinned
comment. Practice for 7 days straight
评论。连续练习7天
and one of you will be entered to win a
你们中的一位将有机会赢得
free 1-year plan of Easy Speak AI. Thank
Easy Speak AI免费一年的使用计划。
you Easy Speak AI for sponsoring today's
感谢Easy Speak AI赞助本期视频。
video.
>> Okay, we're headed through the
好的，我们正穿过
underpass.
地下通道。
to the hot springs. Okay, so we are at
去温泉。好了，我们现在在
Radium Hot Springs that started in 1914
Radium温泉，这里始于1914年。
here. And the hotring is actually
温泉池实际上就位于
located right there.
那里。
So that's just where the pool is, but
那只是泳池的位置，
the source of the hotring is in these
温泉的水源就在附近的这些
mountains right here nearby. And they
山脉中。
just bring the warm water and fill up
他们把温水引过来，注入
this pool. So this is the hotring, and
这个泳池。所以这就是温泉池，
it's a pretty popular one. Half of it is
这里相当受欢迎。现在有一半
closed right now for renovation, but
正在装修关闭，
this half is open. That water doesn't
另一半是开放的。那水看起来
even look that warm, though. I don't see
并不算热，我没看到
any steam coming out. And it's pretty
有蒸汽冒出。外面还挺冷的。
cold out here. So So that's an empty
所以那是个空泳池。
pool.
你看泳池是空的。那个滑梯
You see the pool's empty. And that slide
是滑进泳池的，但我猜…
slides into the pool, but I guess
they're cleaning it. Yeah, there's a
他们正在清理。是的，那边有一个跳板。
diving board right there. And they're
他们正在清理游泳池，所以池里没有水。
cleaning the pool, so there's no water
希望他们能尽快恢复使用。
in the pool. Hopefully they have that up
这些都是加拿大的国家公园。
and running soon. So these are all the
这个地区这里有很多国家公园。
national parks in Canada.
我们现在就在这里。
So there's a lot in this area right
这里是阿尔伯塔省和不列颠哥伦比亚省边界上的落基山脉。
here. And this is where we are right
在北部的各个地区也有很多国家公园。
now. This is like the Rocky Mountains on
我很确定这是北美最大的国家公园。
the border between Alberta and British
看起来很大。
Columbia.
它叫做阿巴斯卡国家公园或者类似的名字。
And you have a lot up here in the north
好的。这里是一个地下通道。你可以看到高速公路在上面，我们从下面走。
in the territories.
所以这是一个行人地下通道。
>> Pretty sure this is the biggest national
这些是不同动物的爪印。
park in North America.
有狼獾的爪印、美洲狮、熊、郊狼，
>> It looks big.
It looks big.
>> It's called Aabaska National Park or
It's called Aabaska National Park or
something.
>> Okay. So, this is an underpass. You can
Okay. So, this is an underpass. You can
see here the highway goes on top and we
walk under it. So, it's an underpass for
pedestrians. And these right here are
paw prints from different animals.
There's a wolverine paw print, a cougar,
pear, coyote,
deer, and wolf. And then on this side,
鹿和狼。然后在这边，
this is a coyote.
这是郊狼。
This is a wolf.
这是狼。
This is a cougar, a deer, and a moose.
这是美洲狮、鹿和驼鹿。
Yeah. And this right here is the This is
是的。这里是……这是
like an overpass. So animals cross here.
一座天桥。动物们从这里穿过。
So instead of crossing over the
所以它们不是穿过
highways, they just cross over right
高速公路，而是直接从这里穿过。
here.
>> Animal crossover.
动物穿越通道。
>> Animal crossing. There you go. There you
动物穿越。就是这样。
go.
就是这样。
>> So animal crossing.
所以是动物穿越。
>> Thank you.
谢谢。
>> So I guess that's that was actually
所以我猜这其实
pretty obvious. Animal crossing. Okay.
很明显。动物穿越。好的。
So technically this is called a wildlife
技术上讲，这叫做野生动物穿越道，
crossing and it's just for animals to
主要是为了让动物能
cross the highway without getting in the
安全穿越高速公路，避免
way of vehicles and getting hit.
干扰车辆或被撞。
So, we've just arrived at our campsite
我们刚到达B国家公园的营地。
in B National Park. Dude, that is a nice
伙计，那座山真漂亮。
mountain. So, that is our view today.
这就是我们今天的景色。
Look at that. And then this is the
看看那个。然后这是
campsite we're in. So, you're making a
我们所在的营地。所以，你正在做一个…
tepee fire.
锥形帐篷火堆。
He's using the the hand torch to start
他正在用手持喷灯点火。
the fire. Okay. So, now my dad is
好的，现在我爸爸正在用一把小斧头砍柴，
chopping wood with a hatchet to make
做火种。
kindling for the fire.
好的，这是一把小斧头，因为它很小。
Okay, so this is a hatchet because this
斧头和它类似，但要长得多。
is small. An axe is similar to this but
但像这样短小的，用于精确切割和制作火种的，
a lot longer.
称为小斧头。
But a short one like this that's used
现在火势真的很旺了。
just for precision cutting and making
好的，大家，我要做烤棉花糖夹心饼干了。
kindling is called a hatchet.
我这里有棉花糖，
But now the fire is really going.
还有我的巧克力饼干。火堆
Okay guys, I'm going to make s'mores. I
有点太大，不太适合做夹心饼干，
have my marshmallows here.
但我觉得只要我把它放在这里，
and my chocolate cookie here. The fire
棉花糖棒上，
is kind of like way too big to make us
我应该能做出一个不错的。
more, but I think if I hold it right
好的，现在把我的棉花糖放到烤棉花糖的棒子上，
here,
或者说我的棉花糖棒上。
>> marshmallow stick,
一个。开始烤它们。
>> I'll be able to make a good one.
现在是时候做我的烤棉花糖夹心饼干了。
>> Okay, now let's put the my marshmallows
Okay, now let's put the my marshmallows
on my marshmallow roasting stick or my
marshmallow stick.
One. Let's cook these up.
So, now it's time to create my s'more
with four marshmallows
用四个棉花糖
because that's the minimum.
因为那是最少的数量。
I've got my s'more here.
我这里有我的烤棉花糖夹心饼。
The rule is always
规则总是
one cracker and four marshmallows.
一块饼干配四个棉花糖。
That way, the chocolate melts.
这样，巧克力才会融化。
It's very
它非常
sticky.
黏糊糊的。
The marshmallow is very sticky.
棉花糖非常黏。
Okay, we're uh we're walking to the bus
好的，我们现在正走向公交车站，
stop right here to catch a bus into town
准备坐公交车进城，
because we don't really want to drive
因为我们其实不太想开露营车进城。
our camper van into town.
是吧，妈妈？
>> Isn't that right, Mom?
是的，我们打算坐公交车进去。
>> Yes, we're going to take the bus in.
进城是免费的，回程要2美元，
It's $2 to come back and free to go, I
我猜是这样。哦，真的吗？
guess. So, Oh, really?
是的。
>> Yeah.
进城免费。我的意思是，
>> Free to go. I mean,
呃，她告诉我的。哦，她说过。
>> uh she told me that. Oh, she said.
是的。回程2美元，我们坐的是2路公交。
>> Yeah. So, $2 to come back and we're on
它会经过Bam Springs酒店。
route two. So, it goes to the Bam
所以，我们应该在
Springs Hotel.
Moose Muskrat North下车，然后接着……
>> So, we should get off like
So, we should get off like
Moose Muskrat North and then then this
is the beginning of town. You can walk
这是镇子的起点。你可以步行
through town
穿过镇子
>> stuff cuz that's we get off here and
东西，因为我们在这里下车，
then this is the whole town. Check your
然后这就是整个镇子。再看看你的地图。几点了
map again. What time
公交车来吗？6:06。我以为
>> the bus comes? 6:06. I thought
我不会准时到。
>> I won't be spot on.
还有10分钟。所以，我们得等
>> It's in 10 minutes. So, we have to wait
大约11分钟。那我们等着吧。
about 11 minutes. So, let's wait.
公交车现在来了。
Bus is coming now.
我猜你是放滑雪装备之类的。
>> I guess you put skier and stuff.
这是费尔蒙酒店。我们能进前门吗？我
>> It's a Fairmont Hotel. Can we get into
想应该可以。
the front? I
应该可以。
>> guess so.
你好。
>> Guess so.
你好，你怎么样？
>> Hi.
往下走。你回来的时候付钱。
>> Hello. How are you?
好的，谢谢。
>> Way down. You pay the way back.
好的，我们现在在公交车上了。
>> Okay. Thanks.
2美元还算不错。
>> Okay, we're on the bus now.
回程的话，2美元基本上是整个行程的费用。或者如果你只坐单程，那是免费的。这是
>> $2 is not not too bad.
一辆公共交通公交车。它是
>> Well, on the way back, $2 for the total
Well, on the way back, $2 for the total
of the trip pretty much. or if you're
only going one way, you'd be free. This
is a public transportation bus. It's
very clean.
非常干净。
Bamp was established as Canada's first
班夫国家公园是加拿大第一个
national park in 1885 and the world's
国家公园，成立于1885年，
third national park in the whole world.
也是世界上第三个国家公园。
It was number three.
它是第三个。
So Canada Goose is one of like the most
加拿大鹅是加拿大最受欢迎的品牌之一，
popular Canadian brands and at one point
曾一度被称为冬季的古驰，
it was known as the Gucci of winter and
它们实际上是一家在多伦多和纽约
they're actually a publicly traded
证券交易所上市的公司。
company on the Toronto and the New York
这些夹克非常昂贵。
Stock Exchange. And these jackets are
这些夹克的平均价格约为1000美元，
very expensive. Like the average price
对于冬季夹克来说非常贵，
of these jackets $1,000, which is very
但我想这也是人们如此喜欢它的原因。
expensive for a winter jacket, but I
班夫国家公园的建立源于
guess that's why people like it so much.
加拿大太平洋铁路工人在硫磺山发现了
So, BA National Park was created after
一个天然温泉，
Canadian Pacific Railroad workers found
随后这里被设立为加拿大的国家公园。
a natural hotring here on Sulfur Mount
所以，它已经是国家公园很长时间了。
and then it was established as a
而我们现在所在的班夫镇，
national park in Canada.
是少数几个实际上位于国家公园内的城镇之一。
>> So, it's been a national park for h for
所以，班夫
a long time.
>> And BA, the town we're in right now, is
And BA, the town we're in right now, is
one of the only towns that are actually
located inside a national park. So, BA
is one, Jasper's one. So, Alberta has
有一个是贾斯珀镇。阿尔伯塔省有
two
两个
>> two towns located in a national park.
两个城镇位于国家公园内。
>> Yeah,
是啊，
>> that's kind of cool.
这挺酷的。
>> It is. Four million people per year
确实如此。每年有四百万人
travel to BA,
前往班夫，
>> which is a lot.
数量相当多。
>> I would believe that. And we're on the
我相信。而且我们现在是淡季，
off season now, so and it's still very
但这里依然很热闹，
>> right now. It's not too busy, but it's
现在不算太忙，但
super busy because the summer it's
夏天的时候非常繁忙，
beautiful for hiking trails. There's
因为那时徒步路线非常美丽。
about 1,600 km of hiking trails or 1,000
夏季大约有1600公里的徒步路线，
mi in the summer. So, there's so much to
约1000英里。夏天有很多活动可做。
do. And in the winter there's
冬天则有
snowboarding, skiing. There's like three
单板滑雪、滑雪。班夫地区内就有三座滑雪山丘。
ski hills just within the VA area. So,
所以，活动非常丰富。
there's a lot to do.
你知道吗？你知道马林湖曾经出现在20美元钞票上吗？
Did you know? Did you know Marine Lake
不知道。它
was once featured on the $20 bill?
曾经印在20美元钞票上。
>> No. It
你知道吗，我们明天要去那里？
>> used to be on the $20 bill.
used to be on the $20 bill.
>> Did Did you know we're going to go there
Did Did you know we're going to go there
tomorrow?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
是的，是的。
>> I didn't actually know that.
我其实不知道这件事。
>> And they used to call it the $20 view,
他们以前称它为“20美元景观”，
>> but I guess they changed it. I don't
但我猜他们改了名字。我现在都不知道20美元钞票上是谁了。
even know who is on the $20 bill
哇。
anymore.
真酷。
>> Wow.
我穿了长裤，所以很暖和，
>> Pretty cool.
但Leon你看他只穿了短裤，
>> I'm very warm cuz I wore long pants, but
我敢肯定他挺冷的。
Leon, you can see he just wore shorts,
不，他是真正的加拿大人。
so I'm sure he's pretty cold.
好的，这就是桥，或者说这就是桥。那是河流。
>> No, he's real Canadian.
这是弓河。就是流经卡尔加里的那条河。
Okay. So, this is the bridge or this is
是的。
the bridge. That is the river. This is
就是流经卡尔加里的那条河。
the Bow River. The same one through
是的。
Calgary.
这就是弓河。
>> Yep.
这条河很漂亮，河面很宽。
>> The same one that runs through Calgary.
看起来很宽，而且水也很浅，
>> Yep.
我能看到这里的河底。
It's the Bow River.
我想知道为什么右边有一堆安全桩。
>> This is a nice river. It's very wide.
This is a nice river. It's very wide.
>> Looks very wide. And it looks very
Looks very wide. And it looks very
shallow, too. Like, I could see the
bottom right here. I wonder why there's
a bunch of safety pylons on the right
hand side of this sidewalk. Should they
这条人行道的右侧。他们应该
close the road off during the day? Look.
白天封路吗？看。
>> So, this is the fun fact. This is the
这是个有趣的事实。这是
highest town in Canada. It sits at for
加拿大海拔最高的小镇。它位于
almost 1,400 m above sea level. So,
海拔近1400米的高度。
it's the highest town in Canada. And I
所以，它是加拿大最高的小镇。
imagine there's a lot of high people
我猜这里也有很多“高”人，
here as well since it's very close to
因为离不列颠哥伦比亚省很近。
BC. If you know, you know.
如果你懂，就懂。
>> If you know, you know. Yeah.
如果你懂，就懂。是的。
>> Caution. Sasquatch crossing.
小心。大脚怪过马路。
So this is a this is a souvenir shop
这里是我们现在所在的纪念品店，
we're in right now and they just sell
他们卖的都是这些叫做纪念品的小东西。
all these little things are called
这里有一些磁铁纪念品。
souvenirs. So here are some magnet
车牌、马克杯、
souvenirs.
巧克力，
License plates, mugs,
还有加拿大非常受欢迎的枫糖浆。
chocolates,
这里有很多纪念品。
maple syrup that's very popular in
驼鹿。
Canada.
一只驼鹿。
A lot of souvenirs here.
驼鹿
>> Moose.
熊。
>> A moose.
A moose.
>> Moose
Moose
bear.
Oh yeah,
哦，是的，
>> a proper one.
一个真正的。
>> This is This is the moose with horns.
这就是带角的驼鹿。
>> Or not horns, with antlers.
不是角，是鹿角。
>> Yeah.
对。
>> What you waiting for?
你在等什么？
>> The bus.
公交车。
>> Okay, so now we are back.
好的，现在我们回来了。
>> We're back at our campsite. Home.
我们回到了我们的营地。家。
>> Back at our campsite.
回到我们的营地。
>> Home for the night.
今晚的家。
>> We're back at our campsite now. We were
我们现在回到营地了。我们刚刚
just in town.
在镇上。
We We got to see the town. Very nice
我们看了看镇子。实际上是个非常漂亮的
town, actually. here. I
镇子。我
>> think it's one of the nicest towns in
认为这是加拿大山区里最漂亮的镇子之一。
the mountains here in Canada.
但现在我们正要回到
>> But now we're heading back to our
营地。
campsite.
希望没有熊来吃我们。如果有的话，希望它先吃
>> Hopefully there's no like bear that eats
里昂，说实话。
us. If there is, hopefully they it eats
嗯，它们吃了这只之后就饱了。
Leon first, honestly.
如果你们想变得更
>> Well, they'll be full after they snack
on this one.
>> If you guys want to become more
If you guys want to become more
confident and sound more natural when
当你说英语时，要自信并听起来自然
you speak English, check out my Patreon.
想了解更多，可以看看我的Patreon。
I post videos there made exclusively
我在那里发布的视频是专门
just to practice your English
用来练习你的英语
pronunciation, your confidence, and your
发音、自信心和
fluency. So, if you guys want to sound
流利度的。所以，如果你们想听起来
fluent in English and become more
英语流利并变得更有
confident, check out my Patreon in the
自信，可以查看描述中的我的Patreon。
description.
>> Yeah, it was nice. Nice. The bus is very
是的，很不错。不错。公交车非常
convenient.
方便。
>> That's probably it for tonight. We're
今晚大概就这样了。我们
just going to relax by this fire now.
现在准备在这火堆旁放松一下。
>> And remember guys, you will become
记住，大家，你们会变得
fluent in English. Their coffee gets
英语流利。他们的咖啡在阿尔伯塔省有售。这是我的卡布奇诺。
sold in Alberta. It's my cappuccino.
这里挺凉爽的。看到那些
>> It's brisk out here. See all those
小卵石了吗？就像这样的小石头。
pebbles? Like a small rock like this.
水面相当波涛汹涌。沿着岸边都是
The water is pretty choppy. All this
泡沫。这些温泉的水源就在这
foam along along the shoreline. The
座山里。现在一半的温泉
source of the hotring is in these
因为装修而关闭，
mountains right here. Half of it is
但另一半是开放的。这是一个空的
closed right now for renovation, but
游泳池。而这些就是爪印。
this half is open. So that's an empty
pool. And these right here are paw
prints from different animals. Hair,
不同动物的足迹。毛发，
coyote. This is like an overpass. So,
郊狼。这就像一个天桥。所以，
animals cross here
动物们从这里穿过
>> to make kindling for the fire. Okay,
去准备生火用的引火物。好了，
guys. I'm going to make s'mores. Now,
伙计们。我准备做烤棉花糖夹心饼干。现在，
let's put the my marshmallows on my
把我的棉花糖放到烤棉花糖的棒子上。它非常
marshmallow roasting stick. It's very
黏，
sticky,
但不会完全粘住。
>> but it won't be spot on.
十分钟后。1885年成立的国家公园。1600公里的徒步小径。20美元钞票。
>> It's in 10 minutes. National Park in
不，
1885. 1,600 km of hiking trails. The $20
它以前印在20美元钞票上。你可以看到他只穿着短裤，所以我敢肯定
bill.
他很冷。这是加拿大海拔最高的城镇。一只驼鹿。
>> No,
No,
>> it used to be on the $20 bill. You can
it used to be on the $20 bill. You can
see he just wore shorts, so I'm sure
he's pretty cold. This is the highest
town in Canada. A moose.